- Congratulations! Jo Na-jeong!
- congratulations!
Look, look
I knew I could make this work!
Competition rate of 100 to 1
Does it make sense to pierce it?
- Is this normal?
- I told you so!
This is not a child who will rot at home
Thank you, friends.
In that sense, I
Top quality wagyu, all beef tongue
Eat as much as you want!
Hmm! it's good!
Thank you, sister
Yes, yes
Hey, but when is Sang-gyu coming?
I don't know!
We can just play together
I just want you to hug me for no reason
How have you been?
The thing about being in Busan
I think I heard it at first glance
What do you think?
Is it a coup? Is it reverse?
Well, it was just the same?
really?
Are you still the goofy artist type?
When I think of Sang-gyu, I think of this
All I can think of is the seaweed head.
My brother probably did it because he thought it was cool.
Like this? uh?
I just passed it like this and just like this...
Hey!
I know, I was a loser
Sang-gyu!
omg! Reverse!
Get on your back! here!
no! Not this one
- Another light!
I need another light!
Right!
Let's stop smoking now and go home.
Come on, get on your back.
Quick! Get on your back! go home
- Come here.
- Wow, I really don't like it.
Ah, let's go home.
Hey, can you carry me?
Okay, let's go first.
- Take care.
- See you later!
Oh, anyway, this girl
If you drink alcohol, other people will
I say I hate everything
Only for Sanggyu hyung and others
I'm carrying you on my back
- Why is that?
- what?
Because I’m drunk, I can do anything on my back.
- He was carried on his back.
- Ah!
hey! Hey, what can I say? you
I hate everything about your other back.
You only looked for my back
- Yeah.
- Yes!
You don't remember?
Oh, it's happening again
Phew
Hey
Sang-gyu, to you
I think you're interested
- What did you say?
- No, that's right.
I only looked at you the whole time
- Hey, try your best.
- Yeah.
Timing is also killing me? uh?
Hey
look at my face
- Chi
- What did you say?
Sang-gyu is as handsome as you, right?
yes
Narangi, Jubal, came
- Oh, yes.
- Yes
Fighting
- Let's go! brother!
- Uh, uh
- See you next time.
- Yes
See you next time, Jubal
Uh, yeah, dragai.
What is it?
I thought it was ugly
Is it worth seeing?
It seems pretty okay
But
My older brother majored in business administration.
How did you become a manual therapist?
Oh no, when I was young
My parents are all out working
I was raised by my grandmother
But when I was 29?
My grandmother had a serious accident.
Because I lost the use of my back
Well, yes
I quit all the plays
Just in Busan
I went down to nurse the child
Well, let the old lady stand up.
Just trying to learn this and that
Well, it just so happened that
We've come this far
Oh, is your neck not sore now?
Ah, yes
Brother, you are good at it.
After receiving treatment, I felt much better.
Thank you, bro.
Well, then I'm glad
But now you
I'm old too, huh?
Drinking anywhere
If you just fall asleep and say no, you can’t do it.
I cut my whole body
Oh my?
When am I?
It was like that when I was young
Not now
smell of alcohol
Go
Now we're there
Where?
why?
Breaking up with me
Is it because you regret it?
What can I say?
What, what?
Want one more drink?
What, is it only today?
What can I say?
Hey, my house is here...
You live here? Brother?
Hey, are you here too...
Wow! No this
It's all a coincidence, really, huh?
No, the house in front is you now?
Does this make sense? This is now
Well, these days it's just neighbors
You don't live by looking at the face, that's just it.
But anyway, it went well.
What's going well?
I worry about your security in the future
You don’t have to, kid, huh?
Strict guys
Just chase after me and then
call me right away
Got it? uh?
What the hell?
Confusingly
Is it flirting?
Oh, that's really interesting, huh?
Then
Please go in
Uh, uh, let's go
But Ilya, maybe later...
What is it?
Why are you trespassing on other people’s houses?
No, if you want me to pack your bags for you.
Give it to me straight away
I don't have a pad
You weren't even able to work.
Then text me
Why without anyone else’s permission?
Are you going in and out of someone else’s house?
I sent it but there was no reply
Oh, I'm really in a hurry.
But who?
Why are you curious about that?
I'm sorry, bro.
Hey, I met you briefly a while ago.
Because I don't like being too obsessed
- It's full.
- Uh
But the password
I forgot to change it
He came into my house like a stalker
Because I was so scared
I pretended to be your boyfriend, sorry.
Uh, no, no, no.
Well done, well done, well done
Ah, creepy
No, it's too annoying
I kept chewing on the phone too.
And then it goes in and out like that.
Yes...
My brother lives next door...
You're welcome.
I was earlier
The child said, he...
Concerns about security
I told you not to, uh
- Did you go?
- Are you gone, just sleep?
- He went.
Went... Went, we went, phew!
Thank goodness!
I'll go then
- Yes
- Uh
yes
Uh, I'll go.
Illya, but this
Wouldn’t it be better to change my password now? That...
If I'm not gone
What if they barge in again?
Well... I guess.
Well then, should I?
Uh, should I change it now?
- That's it.
- Ah...
Meeting you after 20 years
It shows all sorts of things.
Hey, what are you talking about?
You were always drunk in college
While I was carrying it around
I saw everything I couldn't see, and then
Ah...
Then
Please go in first
You go in first.
yes
Then
Hey, you...
If something really happens to me
You have to call me right away, okay?
Right...
yes
hello
“Sweet Home Shopping”
Premature baby!
You caught it too!
congratulations!
what? Did you catch it too?
Yeah
hello
In the future, I will be your
Arranging the internship process
This is team leader Kim Tae-jeong.
During the 3-month internship course,
you meet a mentor
You will receive individual guidance.
Marketing meetings along the way
Partner meeting, broadcast observation, etc.
actual work
you will learn
Until here
Do you have any questions?
If not, I'll skip it.
Ah...
I'm so nervous I can't even sigh at night
I can't sleep and I'm dying from exhaustion.
Who will be your mentor?
In this world, if you meet the wrong mentor,
Rather than burning a nurse
They say it hurts more
Still, we only tried Labang
I desperately need your help.
We must make good use of this opportunity.
You did Labang.
Wow, cool
I'm going to Labang too
I just looked everywhere
I'm running out
What kind of labang did you do?
Can I ask?
Oh my, senior, hello!
oh! Minjoo, Seonyoung
How are you?
I heard you're coming back again.
How do you feel? How do you feel about your return?
Wow, what kind of comeback?
I'm still an intern
Hey, senior
It's a given.
I haven't watched the main broadcast
Are you like people?
Ah, me too from the beginning
It's like starting again
Well then, enjoy your meal.
Yeah, go
Yeah
Ah
That...
What is it?
It feels strangely dirty
No, well then
We're all wearing hot pants
Can you see it?
No, I didn't mean that.
That’s it!
You have this one
You better keep that in mind
you're from here
Well, if you get special treatment then
me then
Are you really staying still?
and!
It's been no joke since day one
It's bloody, it's bloody
Ah, Managing Director
As for mentor Jo Na-jeong,
I really don't want to do it.
Oh, I really hate that girl!
Even in the past, we were not compatible
There was a big fight
You know it very well, Mr.
Now the mentor is the mentee
Where can you choose and sleep?
Just do it when given.
Then, eat it boiled or baked instead.
Can I do whatever I want?
Either that
As if I were a senior again
Just leave me alone
Very snappy! I have to drop it
What is it?
IC
Uh, what is it? What happened?
Did you go out with Sang-gyu for a bit?
Hey, I think I'm pregnant.
- Just now?
- no! crazy
Not Sang-gyu.
What does that mean?
No, I'm out of my mind these days.
I couldn't pay attention
Have you not had your period?
It's been three months
But it's safe at that point
How many times have you not used a condom?
Wow, are you a teenager?
Oh, what should I do!
That guy has already left his mind
What about the test?
Oh, that's right! test!
What happened?
It's one line
Oh, look! It's a girl
You were surprised! what?
But why don't I have my period?
Three months?
I wonder if it’s menstrual irregularity
First, get a checkup first.
And you go to sleep, okay?
Early menopause?
Recent menstrual flow
It has decreased a lot and has become irregular.
I'm very irritable, so I need to control my emotions
Wasn’t it difficult?
No, well...
I think it was like that
The blood test results are very bad.
If you look here, the AMH level is
It's almost at the bottom
This is a follicle that is about to ovulate
That means there are almost none.
So how can we delay it?
Not at the moment
It's okay
Originally, I had no intention of having a child.
It wasn't there in the first place
Because I don't menstruate
There are also some that are a bit more comfortable.
I had really bad menstrual cramps.
If it overlaps with the deadline, ugh...
hell, hell
Open your face!
Am I really okay?
What do you want to say?
speak quickly
It's on air soon
Ah, yes
Uh, it's Yena.
I may not feel like it, but
Because I will try really hard
please lead me
I know too
you are uncomfortable
Once upon a time we
We hurt each other
That person is an intern
How much I hate it
But, I've been there for 6 years
I took a break and came out
I really forgot everything
You don't know anything
I think about teaching my juniors.
Can you please lead me?
Oh, sir, what should I do?
I heard the demonstration model had a puncture.
What?
why?
They say there was a contact accident and it's being resolved.
They say it will take two hours
There's not much left to broadcast
I didn't do it, so what should I do?
What about other models?
Wasn’t it the previous broadcast Beauty?
- He said he had already left work and was out of town.
- Ha...
Well, without a demonstration
Look at me
Are you telling me to beat the drums and play the janggu now?
Maybe...
What if I try that?
I took a long break, but at least the demonstration was
I think I can do it
- Do you want to do that?
- Uh
What exactly was it?
Break up
Oh, hair products?
Oh, then make a before
I’ll go in quickly!
now
What were you doing?
Earlier, it was a hair product.
Didn't you?
Me?
When?
PD Kim
Did I say it was a hair product?
uh?
Uh... no?
Ha...
Oh, what?
Is this ridiculous?
Why did my sister put it wrong?
Are you blaming us?
It's just a mistake
You can just admit it.
- Ah...
- I'll take care of it.
Sister, please leave.
Whitening, wrinkle improvement
UV protection, triple functionality...
Grandma Illi Lee, who turned 80 this year,
Today too, I only eat rice with water.
I survive on meals.
Because I have never been married in my life
no family
Grandma is the only one
time to talk
once a month
The only time the social worker visits
Aren’t you lonely?
I miss people
I can't even speak
Well, if you say so,
Even at a nearby church...
Wherever old people go
I'm not welcome
If you knew I would be like this
Should I at least get married on time?
I also want to
No! Ouch!
Why are you doing this?
What's going on?
no
Wow, I was surprised.
Wow, my heart hurts
What's going on?
Elijah
are you okay?
yes, mother
Didn’t you call me in when you were busy?
No
I was about to leave work after work too.
Because I ate dinner with my mother.
It's so good, well
thank you
I went out shopping nearby, took a moment
I called because I wanted to see your face.
I guess there is no overtime today?
Yes, these days, whatever, preferably.
I'm trying not to.
Oh, yes!
Well done, well done
Even so, your body is weak.
How worried were you that you might overdo it?
Women working overtime, dieting
It's the root of all ills.
Wow, eat a little more
yes
There's no problem with the couple's relationship these days, right?
yes, what
Oh!
I was walking around the department store today
Perfect!
I have something for you
Uh, thank you, mom.
What is it?
Spread it out
uh?
how is it?
Pretty, right?
yes
No matter what a woman does
Your stomach should be warm
I saw you when you were there
These palm-sized panties
They said they were wearing it
Oh, then I can’t use it!
I handled the broadcast well.
My sister has the latest products
what kind of things are there
Start by organizing the list and familiarize yourself with it.
Organize your categories
Until work time
Send it to me
- But you told me earlier...
- Does that matter now?
I almost got into an accident
Don't you have enough?
This is ridiculous.
Ah!
later in the evening
With Team Jinguk and Managing Director Seo
Because there is a company dinner
Please attend
Dinner?
why?
Can’t you come out again?
no, no
No, what are you talking about?
Suddenly there is no one to watch the kids
I asked my aunt for a favor.
My son-in-law and daughter are coming.
They say you can never come
Aww, baby
I'd rather just
Can't I leave it to my mother-in-law?
How does a mother look after three children?
No, how can I do that?
Are you canceling the meeting?
Anyway, I can't do it today.
- Ugh...
- I have to go, sorry.
Ah, honey!
What if I just go?
Baby...
uh
Uh, mom
What's wrong?
Taerin got caught in hand, foot and mouth.
I couldn't even go to kindergarten
Your sister-in-law is having such a hard time
I'm drowning in death
Oh, I see.
Is the company worth going to?
Uh, uh, then
Oh my, your sister-in-law
Another call comes in, hang up first.
Okay, mom, I'll call you back.
Uh, Najeong.
Uh, sister
Uh...
I...
I have a favor to ask...
uh
Wow
Oh, even though it’s okay, it’s a hassle for no reason
You can come by bus.
No
Mother carries this heavy burden alone
How do you carry it?
Hey, do you want to go in?
No, Mr. Sangmin.
I have to go before it comes.
Oh, wait a minute
I want to give it to you
I got something precious
Just wait a moment, okay?
Youngah Joo
Now, this
I went to a monk I know.
She wrote one for her daughter-in-law.
I feel like my energy is low
I'm so depressed these days, I'm dying, what?
What sin did you commit in your past life?
I wonder if you don't have any kids
Even when I think about that while I'm sleeping
My solar plexus is sore
It doesn’t feel bad, does it?
no, mother
Of course
yes
My monthly life mask in Jeju Island is
To Sangmin, I gave him a flower.
Could you please ask me to give you some water?
yes
It doesn't go far
go
I'll go see it
Chi
It's your son's fault.
Why don't you think about it?
Because what do you think I will say?
Now you've ordered it back to your home, right?
What did you buy again this time?
Ouch! ah! ah!
Ah...
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Yes, thank you for your hard work.
How long do I have to wait?
I haven't finished it yet
Can't you just wait a little longer?
Okay, then
Just finish it
Please send it by email
uh
But
Aren't you hungry?
Uh...
Well, a company dinner
It's done at Galbijip.
It would be a waste to eat something flimsy.
Well then, see you later.
Hey, why do you keep eating from my cup?
This is mine, the red cup!
Aunt
Huh?
Is this him?
Don't touch me at all
Yoo Ah Young
You can't use it like that
I am a guest who came to my house.
You should lend me some cups too.
Why doesn't mom take my side?
Do you keep taking Noh Min-woo’s side?
I hate you mom!
Ouch!
our princess
Why did I lose my temper again?
huh?
Our Ayoung, do you listen well?
Okay
nice
Ouch!
Are you here?
Let's eat
When are you going home?
Oh, the lady is a little busy today.
Why?
Mom, did you forget that it’s exam period for me?
If you look at them all...
What should I do?
I understand
Eat
I don't eat with them.
take it to the room
Huh?
Hey, Yoo Bo-hyun!
We are so thankful
Wow
Sorry, sorry...
- Oh, are you here?
- Yes
- sit, sit
- Yes, yes.
President Kim
Is this him?
Who is it?
In the past, I really
He was a promising prospect.
But then I gave birth
I mean, you disappointed me so much.
- Hey, Jo Na-jeong.
- Yes
I know
As a working mom, you are a senior.
I really hoped you would do well.
So it was harsher
But
This bastard, this
In the end, I couldn't hold on and quit.
Did you quit because of me?
Oh no, Mr. Manager.
Then why did you quit?
sorry
I lacked grit
You can do better this time, right?
Yes, I will work hard.
Okay, okay!
In that sense, we
Let's go fighting!
boss
Karaoke is okay, right?
Ah, of course!
Now, let's go!
- Let's go, let's go.
- Let's go
Of course! Boss Kim!
- ♪ Yesterday too ♪
- ♪ Today too ♪
♪ Tomorrow too ♪
- ♪ As always! ♪
- ♪ What you want to hear, words, words! ♪
♪ You like me ♪
- ♪ I like it! ♪
♪ I like you ♪
♪ You like me ♪
- ♪ I like it! ♪
♪ I like you ♪
Bravo!
ruler! Now, now, everyone.
Now at this point
Our Najeong
Let's try singing!
clap!
♪ Now I’m smiling
smile again ♪
♪ It's a happy moment
happy days ♪
♪ Straighten your shrunken shoulders
In this world ♪
♪ Erase all the hard work ♪
♪ Forget about sadness
never cry ♪
♪ Under the hot sun
sunny days ♪
♪ Always only good things
Just hope it's full ♪
Oh, heungnajeong!
I have high expectations for you
As much as it was difficult to come back
Working two or three times harder than others
Okay, let's go in.
- Managing Director
- Yes
Why?
Do I have to go?
sorry
The schedule was a little messed up
Are you going?
uh? Uh...
Oh, go, then
True
One place for a dinner party
I won't be able to protect it till the end
Why did you join the company?
why do i
Should I be kicked out to the reading room?
If I fail this exam
Is mom going to take responsibility?
Why are you being so sensitive?
If the lady is a little busy
Can you babysit the kids?
Mom says my daughter is taking a test
Do friends come first?
If you are going to leave your child at someone else's house
Don't work!
Oh, how selfish you are!
Oh my, this girl
I thought everything was just words...
I... Bohyun
I'm sorry, Najeong.
Kid...
Bohyun is going through puberty these days.
We fight over everything.
no
I'm more sorry, okay?
Without even noticing
Bohyeon didn’t even know it was exam period.
Hey, hey! don't mind!
Without studying at all
That's right, I just found an excuse.
Have you even had dinner yet?
Oh no
Hey, go eat
No, sister
I'm not hungry
Wow, curry anyway
If you use up a lot and have everything left, throw it away.
I eat it thinking it will reduce my drinking.
Well!
Ugh
What should I do because it’s hard?
Uh...
Uh, this
Looks like I bought a new bowl
I didn't see it
Najeongah
Still, Najeong
Hold on as long as you can
If I hold on just a little longer and the kids grow up
Holding on now
You'll feel lucky
Hey, actually, at first I
When Bohyun was born and I quit the company
Oh no
Was it really difficult back then?
But then
Do you know what was the most difficult thing?
Hmm...
Feeling of alienation from society
Oh, that's just like that
I couldn't bear it
But before it's too late
You took the chance
What a precious opportunity.
Hold on
Hold on as long as you can
Me and Minwoo and Minjun
I didn't do it reluctantly.
Hey, anyway, you are my dream now
Instead, I'm making it happen
Huh?
Hey, but how can I
How can I not support you?
And the Jo Na-jeong I know
This is how difficult it is to work
I'm not the kind of person who falls apart
Cheer up, Jo Na-jeong!
Wow
Baby, eat quickly
This won't taste good if it cools down.
Even if you want to eat it quickly
Thanks, sister
Yena!
Did you go well yesterday?
It ended too late, right?
Have you prepared for the meeting?
Oh, well then! let's go
Uh, come on
Ouch! Oh, what!
If you give me a latte
What should I do, make me fat!
That
Americano only
Did you see me eating?
Uh, sorry.
It seems like I don't eat much these days.
I'm afraid I'll feel sick
I'll ride you again!
Okay, that's it.
Have you thought about some ideas?
This and that while I'm at home
There must have been a lot of input.
uh
While I'm at home
There is a product I looked at carefully.
fully automatic indoor bike
If you just put your foot on the pedal
move automatically
Ah, who buys something like this!
I live to exercise
If your bike is automatic
Would this be exercise?
Hey, listen to the end
my mom a few years ago
Did you have knee surgery?
So for a while
You went to rehab.
This is for the helpless elderly
It's so useful
Our home shopping main customer base is
They're in the middle age group.
The way I see it...
Oh, not so good.
The managing director identifies the age of the main customer base.
I said let's lower it.
Rather, something like a luxury bag or sunglasses.
I don't know if it's something like this
Hey, definitely not sunglasses
Why?
Sunglasses are pretty at best
Do you suit yourself?
You can't tell if it doesn't suit you.
If a return is received for no reason, the risk is high.
That's what my sister thought.
That's not the trend these days.
Ugh, not very nutritious.
I have no ideas
Ha...
Now
Then the monthly meeting is
I decided to end it here
Well, now you're free
When we launch it on our channel
Item that seems good
Let's talk
Quickly, quickly, give your opinion
now we
In product preoccupation
They're falling behind us by a long way.
A report has been posted
Everyone has a sense of ownership
We must join forces to survive!
Managing Director
Our mentee presentation
Can I order it?
Who is the mentee?
It's me
This is Yang Mi-sook, an intern.
Let's talk
I don't know anything else
To this luxury product
Because it’s a crisp container
I'm telling you
This time in Hercules
We released a new model of sunglasses.
- Look at it.
- Yes
It went down really well, right?
As soon as this came out
It's completely sold out.
In other home shopping
before monopolizing
What we take first is
I wonder what it would be like
I...
I'm against it.
No matter how many sunglasses
Even if it’s luxurious and pretty
Without trying it
Does it suit you?
Doesn't suit me
It's hard to judge
If you buy something because it’s pretty and the return rate increases,
I think the risk is high.
Rather, I recently
There is one product that was a big hit.
It's a fully automatic indoor bicycle.
Huh!
Yeah
When you put your feet on the bicycle wheel
pedal automatically
It moves me.
Automatically?
well
A bike that doesn't even work
Who buys it?
Elderly people who have had knee surgery
After surgery
mostly automatically
moves the legs
Get rehabilitation treatment.
How good is the effect?
You knew me well
As you know
The power of the elderly in home shopping is
Because you can't ignore it
Um...
yes
That's a valid opinion.
Choi MD, contact the company.
From now on, you too, like Song Shoho
Don't be limited to your field
If there is a good item
Actively express your opinion
yes, i understand
Hey!
Anyway
Isn't this too much?
fully automatic indoor bike
It was my idea
Why do you talk like it's yours?
What do you mean?
Who are you treating as a thief?
The intern came up with that little idea.
What a great thing!
And the team did it
- Did you do it?
- what?
A little idea like that?
Do you have an idea?
Can you pay?
Have you said everything?
Look at this, look at this
At some point, he asked me to pull and push something.
I can't go on like this
Mentee evaluation report
I'm going to use it, so get ready to cut it.
What is me
Do you know how to stay still?
Fuck like a beggar one more time
You are the one causing bullying in the workplace
I know I'll get sued
And you
Last time, it was a hair product.
They lied to me and accused me of it.
Do you think I just passed it over because I didn't know anyone?
Huh...
I guess I'm crazy
You must be crazy! Are you crazy!
Song Yena
how dare you
Touching the nose hair of a sleeping lion?
you are dead to me now
MD Choi
yes
How are you going to sell that?
Well, it's a trick to make other things
I can't even bring it
So?
How ripe are the apples now?
It's still blue
This is in line with shipment
The broadcast date has been set.
- Because of the abnormal temperature...
- So what do you want to do?
In this empty studio
Are you going to broadcast it?
uh? Pre-order, post-delivery
Just hang up this sign? uh?
What on earth are you trying to seduce me with? What!
- uh?
- PD Kim
What if it were like this?
We are broadcasting in an orchard.
Then with other items
There is no need to replace
The visuals are pretty too
It seems plausible, right?
Fresh seasonal fruits
Delivered immediately after harvest
I can also give you faith
It's so good, isn't it?
how is it? How do you feel, PD?
fresh seasonal fruits
So, is that a good idea?
Right? Right?
Oh, what's okay?
I'll do that one
You want to go to the countryside?
Oh, I hate it.
Find another way
Then, senior
Do you have any good ideas?
As of now
I think that's the best
yes, right now
There is no alternative
Well, otherwise
Is there any alternative that comes to mind?
Ah...
You're thinking about it now! now!
Just think about it little by little...
Where is the time to think? huh?
Just go ahead and do it.
Well, MD Choi is with that company.
Please adjust the schedule and let me know.
yes, i understand
- Fresh seasonal fruits
- Yes
- Good idea
- Ugh
Well then, good job
Fresh seasonal apples
Fresh seasonal apples...
Ai!
hmm!
I need to look at that technical book.
Don't drive rough
yes
Sheesh, I'm the mentor.
Are you your servant?
Make me drive and go crazy
But did you spray perfume?
yo. this?
I'm a little worried about that.
Who cares about whom?
Intern Jo, don’t meddle in other people’s business.
Do your own thing
Are you thinking of doing it right?
yes
“Key Features & Benefits”
It's all over
Are you going to wait here any longer?
Oh, it's so hot outside
Call me when I’m on standby
yes
Oh my, you bastard!
The show host didn't even watch the scene.
Are you going to broadcast?
hmm!
What do you eat alone?
Do you even manage it?
why?
Can you give me one?
That's enough
Sal is Jo Intern.
Because it seems more urgent
Well, it's smarter than starving.
Right?
Ah...
Where is the bathroom?
Hey there
Wow!
Ugh! Wow! Wow!
Wow, really!
Wow
After...
Argh!
Ouch!
omg!
Puha!
Argh!
uh!
Oh my face
It feels like it's burning!
Yes, it's 119, right? Buy here...
Oh, really!
The vehicle went somewhere else
They said they couldn't come!
cadet! What should I do? What should I do?
What should I do with my face?
I'm not dying, right?
What if I have anaphylaxis?
What if I get cut from the broadcast?
What should I do with my broadcast?
- Sister!
- Uh, uh
- I think I'm losing my mind.
Sister, I think I'm going to pass out.
- I'm out of my mind...
- Oh!
- oh! no!
- I'm out of my mind...
No, no, no!
hey! Song Yena, come to your senses!
You can't lose your mind!
The hospital is here!
Then why are you wearing perfume?
no! no!
no! quickly, quickly, quickly
Don't lose your mind!
Oh, really!
Oh, hey...
Here! Emergency!
I got stung by a bee!
Hey, hey! you!
Where are you going!
What should I do with the broadcast? It has to be broadcast!
Hey, you! it's crazy?
Oh, you're saying it's Anamachine?
Oh, nothing like that! Let go!
Oh, really!
Car keys!
-Give me the car keys.
- Oh, I can't give it to you!
You with a face like this
How are you going to broadcast it?
Treatment must be done first!
What do you do with treatment?
If I mess up on air, I'll get fired!
I already got some ugly hair!
If the broadcast goes on like this,
I'm really done!
How did I get up here!
My sister has a child!
I also have a husband!
But I
The only thing I have to do is work!
Oh...
- Breathing...
- Oh!
I really can't breathe...
I thought there was no such thing...
Hey Yena!
oh my god! Here!
Yena!
yes, thank you
Yes, Managing Director!
Jo Na-jeong!
where are you now?
Oh, I'm at the hospital now.
Yeah, it seems to be getting better...
Then
Run to the farm right now!
Who can broadcast now?
I have to do it because it's only you.
Can you do it?
Ah... me?
Have you read the product description? Didn't you?
Answer quickly!
No time!
I'm done
On-site awareness
I did everything, but
Great! Then, jump out now!
If you don't do this
Not only me, but also Kim Tae-jung and Song Yena
And everyone, including you
Do you understand?
Yes, Managing Director
uh
I was familiar with all product descriptions.
The price is 32,900 won
Packed in air pocket
The sugar content is over 14 Brix.
- Yes
- Uh
Average weight is 250g
New apples harvested for the first time this year
The free gift is 20 packs of apple juice.
You can also purchase it if you want
That's right!
Hodori! Let's get ready!
yes!
- Ugh!
- Hehe!
cadet! uh!
Ugh, ha...
Ah...
Huh? uh! Wait a minute!
sorry! sorry!
Oh, sorry!
10 seconds before broadcast!
Wow
5 seconds ago!
Hello, customers.
This is Jo Na-jeong, a shopping host.
Today is special
Under clear and clear weather
In Ungyeong
Greetings from the apple farm
Now, do you guys see it?
Apples on every tree
It's wide open
This refreshing scenery
directly to you
I want to show you
It says it like this
The apples you are looking at now
I'm preparing hard
Get ready for the flavor to soar
And get ready for the colors to get deeper
Come on!
Everyone, please apologize.
You think they are all similar, right?
The apple taste is
in what land
How much sunshine have you received?
- And when...
- Oh my!
- Depending on the harvest
- Oh my! oh! oh!
completely different
- What is the scenery here?
- Oh my, my.
The daily temperature difference is large
The flesh is hard
It has the advantage of being crunchy.
So the sugar content is high
The sour taste is subtle
Famous for its balanced taste
Sweet home shopping, right?
What's being broadcast now
-I want to order something.
- This fresh and refreshing scent!
I'll give it a try
Well!
- Everyone, can you hear me?
- yes yes!
The texture is crunchy and juicy!
It's alive, it's alive
I won't talk much longer
I'll show you the composition today.
Now, the first harvest of the year, Ungyeong Premium.
A box of 5 kg fresh apples
If you order now
Only 32,900 won!
Because it's a pre-order
We just lowered the price drastically.
You can also go to the local direct market.
This condition is absolutely difficult to meet
in the first week of next month
Harvested when the taste is at its peak.
Right from the source
I'm planning to send it to you
How to do it
Is this price possible?
People who think like this
There must be a lot.
What about today’s broadcast?
We negotiate closely with the farm.
Specially organized before official shipment
Because it's a broadcast
This condition is
This benefit is only available today
Never forget!
ah!
Currently 800 minutes!
You are ordering
The average sugar content is
14 brix or more
Unkyung apple unique
Sweet and refreshing taste
If you receive it, it will probably be sent directly from the place of origin.
You will be amazed at how different it is.
Oh!
The moment I tell you
Customers who purchased now
It's over 1,000 minutes! yes
Agent connection
that there may be a delay
Please understand.
You can also order via app
You know, right?
Ah...
- Oh my, thank you for your hard work.
- Oh, yes, thank you.
- I enjoyed it so much.
- Oh, yes, no.
Yes, please come in.
- Thank you for your hard work, senior.
- Uh, Taejeong.
- Oh, what about Yena?
- Oh, it's okay.
They say my face has sunken now.
Ah, thank goodness
I'm sorry by the way
I can't even sell it out
Uh, what?
80% of sales
In this situation, this is enough
Well, it's almost a miracle
Kid...
I forgot, senior ability.
You always helped me when I was in trouble.
Oh, what do you mean?
I have some apple juice left.
Would you like some?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Yes
Yes, hello?
Are you on your way up?
Yes, we're almost there now.
Then
I'll just keep things simple.
I saw you today
Stop observing now
I thought it would be okay to broadcast it.
Because there is also an issue of equity.
The main is difficult, starting with the sub
Are you okay?
Ah, yes
Welcome back, Jo Na-jeong
Because the future is more important
don't relax
yes
I will keep this in mind, Manager.
thank you
Cool, right?
It's small, but it's really cool.
What's going on?
No PD
Najeong, you're in the suite.
You don’t like it, right?
Can't you let me go?
what?
Why are you alone again?
Are you writing a novel?
These days, they don’t say let’s do it.
I'm actually relieved.
What are you doing here?
Why take it off!
Unnie, I'm a fan of Wang.
When you suddenly call me
Baby, you’re in menopause now.
Now sanitary pads
I don't need it
Most importantly
What requirements do you think
If you could tell me
Phil?
I cut it and Yang Mi-sook
Did you ask me to make you a sub?
Yes, my sister is with me too
There's no difference.
You are your mentor
They say they can't contact me
Why are you so calm?
Yena! Yena!